person.com 2007-02-10

# Person.com: Frequently Asked Questions

| 

|  |  |  |  |  [make us your homepage]() |  |  234873 members |  |  2367 members online |  |  [bookmark us]() |  |  support  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  | 

**Keeping your privacy is very important to us.**

|   
---|---|---  
This Privacy Policy is to ensure that your privacy is protected while using our Site.  
Please make sure to read the Site's [Terms & Conditions](http://person.com/faka.phtml?id=terms) as well.  
  
|  | 

**What Information Do We Collect?**

|   
---|---|---  
\- When you chose to join the site, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your email address.   
\- We also collect your IP address.   
\- Finally, we collect and keep your login and password (the information you need to use the site) as well as any publications you post on the site for others to view. For example: if you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users' comments about you in our complaints department. 

You should know that your email information can't be accessed or used by the public to send you direct messages. All users can send you email only by using person.com message system.   
  
|  | 

**How Do We Use Your Information?**

|   
---|---|---  
\- We may internally use the personally identifiable information collected on our users to improve our marketing, to improve our content and products and to customize our site to our users. This allows us to improve our site and meet your needs.   
\- We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests.   
\- We also send periodic informational updates and promos to our consenting users via email.   
\- Our departments (for example our Customer Service Department) may use personally identifiable information to answer your questions, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms & Conditions.   
  
|  | 

**When Do We Disclose Your Information?**

|   
---|---|---  
Obviously, in case we are required by law enforcement agencies and or in case we are required to enforce intellectual property or other rights, we may disclose your information.  
  
|  | 

**How Can You Update or Delete Your Information?**

|   
---|---|---  
You have the following choices to update or delete your information from our database: You may log in with your password and update or delete your profile. Please note that the information is not deleted from the Company's database but will be saved under a deleted status and will not be presented.  
  
|  | 

**What about Public Forums?**

|   
---|---|---  
Person.com makes message boards available to its users and visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personally identifying information.   
  
|  | 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

|   
---|---|---  
Person.com users may use the following options for removing their information from our database if they do not wish to receive future communications.   
1\. Use our bugreport system; or  
2\. Use your "[account overview](http://person.com/profile/overview.phtml?msection=my_account&menu=pulldown) to delete your account. Scroll to the bottom of the page and press "Suspend My User Account".  
  
|  | 

**Acceptance of Privacy Statement**

|   
---|---|---  
Your use of our website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy statement and the Terms and Conditions. BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of any portion of our website following posting of the updated privacy statement will constitute your acceptance of the changes.  
  
|  | 

**Questions?**

|   
---|---|---  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
